{
    "subject": "Edmund_Lowe",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Lilyan_Tashman",
    "human_readable": "Edmund Lowe is married to Lilyan Tashman.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9437628984451294,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Edmund Lowe and Lilyan Tashman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9171068668365479,
            "question": "Who is married to Lilyan Tashman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.916841447353363,
            "question": "Is Lilyan Tashman married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8947198390960693,
            "question": "Who was Edmund Lowe married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7946446537971497,
            "question": "Name one famous actor who was married to Lilyan Tashman."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7930135130882263,
            "question": "Was Edmund Lowe ever married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7007586359977722,
            "question": "What was the name of Edmund Lowe's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6776560544967651,
            "question": "What is the name of Edmund Lowe's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02812628634274006,
            "question": "Are there any famous couples from the Golden Age of Hollywood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.018468713387846947,
            "question": "Who are some notable figures in Hollywood history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edmund Lowe is married to Lilyan Tashman.",
            "html": "yago_11279_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous couples from the Golden Age of Hollywood?",
            "html": "yago_11279_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Edmund Lowe's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_11279_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Edmund Lowe's wife?",
            "html": "yago_11279_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11279_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11279_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11279_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11279_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11279_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11279_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11279_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11279_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11279_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11279_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Edmund Lowe is married to Lilyan Tashman.\" Multiple sources confirm their marriage, including newspaper articles and a description of a photo taken in 1933 showing Edmund Lowe and his wife Lilyan Tashman."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}